Yoo Jung!
I miss you.
You're still the same,
but I'm getting old.
I'm afraid that I might forget you.
I'm afraid of being that kind of person.
What should I do?
Where is San?
Is he okay?
Let's get in the car.
Do Hoon, what about my dad?
He's at a nursing home.
Let's go to see him now.
Can we go get San first?
He might have forgotten my face.
What?
Nothing. I just can't believe that you're here with me.
When you told me that your mother visited San at the orphanage,
I was hoping that she could bring him to me.
But I thought it's not a good place for him to visit.
Outside is much better anyway.
That's what I told myself.
How are you?
Fine.
I guess San is a big boy now.
Babies grow every day.
Did you take lots of pictures?
Why didn't you send me any?
He had septicemia
When they contacted me...
San!
Don't do this.
Let me go! You're lying.
He's not dead.
Bring San back to me.
Yoo Jung! Listen to me!
Do Hoon! I need to find San.
We need to find him.
San is dead! He's dead!
You're lying! Stop lying!
I knew you would be desperated.
I knew how sad you are.
I did it all for you.
I lied to you to save you.
My mother said she scattered his ashes here.
It's also my first time here.
I couldn't conjure up the courage to come myself.
I'm sorry that I didn't tell you earlier.
Stop!
So troublesome.
How dare they come to my house?
Darn it!
Father!
You scared me.
Why didn't you tell us?
I had to fool you first to fool the prosecutors.
Se Yeon, I'm glad you're here.
You know that K Hotel bid for the official hotel
for the World Forum.
Yes.
This will decide whether K Hotel becomes
a world class hotel or not.
To persuade the judges on this bid,
I need your help, Se Yeon.
Prepare together with Se Yeon.
You should've told me earlier.
Then where were you so early in the morning?
Who's the guy keep investigating us?
It's Ahn Do Hoon,
who was in charge of Congressman Kim's investigation.
What?
I'll tell Mr. Yang to handel it.
No.
Give him some more time.
Let him squirm enough so we can know if he's a dragon or a snake.
How can he be a dragon?
I think he's an earthworm.
An earthworm living in wet, dirty soil.
He'll come out when it rains,
we should bake him till death.
Shin Se Yeon!
Are you still concerned about her?
She already paid for what she did in jail.
Why do you keep on doing this?
How can she pay for a person's life?
It's a terrible obsession.
What should I do?
I'm still angry.
Why are you so angry?
Think about it.
Do you still miss Seo Ji Hee,
or do you want to pass on your guilt to someone else?
It's so dirty here.
I can't...
Nobody has lived here for so long.
There is no room for me to stand.
You should eat. Go ahead!
Don't cry.
If you're too attached to him, he may not be able to go to heaven.
Let him go so that he can be happy in heaven.
He has already dead.
You should live on as well.
I know how you feel.
I lost my first daughter.
She just learnt how to walk.
I was too busy with work to take care of her.
I had to make a living.
People talked behind my back,
I didn't care what they said.
They don't live for me.
They only scold me.
No one really cared about me.
Yoo Jung, think about your father.
You should live on.
After getting through this,
there won't be anything that you can't handle.
Trust me.
Stop crying.
You'd better go home now.
Do you think I'm being mean?
Who do you think Yoo Jung needs the most?
Someone she can cry with?
She needs someone who can make her strong and help her keep on living.
She has to be strong.
I know.
Do you know why...
Please stop.
Give her some time to mourn.
Please go.
You should think about yourself when she gets better.
Isn't it too early to be drinking?
Where is Yoo Jung? Is she okay?
I don't think I can face her.
Why?
I just can't understand why she did it.
She is so obedient,
and likes Do Hoon so much.
Why didn't she tell Do Hoon about the kid at first?
Why did she send him to an orphanage?
Is that the Yuejeong I know?
How can she be so cruel!
Maeybe she didn't dare to see us.
How can she not dare to see us
with such a grandson?
I didn't even have a chance to hold him in my arms.
If I knew he would leave us so soon, I'd have joined you when you visited him.
San, I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry that I couldn't protect you.
I'm sorry that I had to let you go alone.
I'm sorry that I couldn't hold you in my arms.
Yoo Jung, eat something, or you would faint.
It's my fault.
San died because of me.
That's nonsense. You didn't kill him.
What should I do? What should I do, Do Hoon?
How can I live without San?
Do Hoon!
I can't live without him.
You should blame me for that.
San! San!
I haven't seen her since she visited the orphanage where her son was.
Do you think I'm too obsessed?
My brother told me not to judge my boss whatever he does.
Is that so? I'm confused.
I know this won't bring Ji Hee back.
I guess there's still more I can take from her.
She's coming.
Yoo Jung! Yoo Jung!
Sorry. I'm so sorry, San.
I'm going to stop crying.
If I keep crying, you won't be able to sleep, right?
I miss you.
I want to touch you and hold you so badly.
It's all my fault.
What?
The stars are so pretty. Right, San?
Yoo Jung, you should've told me before you going somewhere.
I was worried about you.
I was worried that...
Sorry, Do Hoon. I forgot that you're as crushed as I am.
I'm okay. Don't worry about me.
As long as I remember him, he'll stay with us.
Go punish the bad guys, San and I will be proud of you.
Go.
Thank you, San. Mommy is happy.
I'm happy because of you.
I'll remember you as long as I live.
Mommy will come and see you later.
- You can't go in! - Stop!
Mr. Jo Min Hyuk, we have evidence that suggests you bribed Congressman Kim Chang Suk.
This is a warrant for search and seizure.
- Take all the files and hard disks. - Yes, sir.
Get to work!
You've gone too far.
You can't use the knife which is used to kill the dog to kill the owner.
What do you think, prosecutor Ahn?
I was about the kill the dog, but then I realized that the owner is much worse.
Catching the owner might help more people.
Sorry to disappoint you, but that's a toy knife.
I didn't want to give the real one to a kid.
Depending on who use it,
a toy can also be dangerous.
What is it that you're holding?
Give it to me.
I don't mind showing it to you,
but you might not like it.
Okay, here you are.
- Hello. - Come back right now!
Don't you understand what I'm saying? Stop what you're doing now and come back.
What a pity.
I really wanted to see how you'd react when you see this.
If we really want to catch them,
we can dig up dirt on them. That's how we work.
There's a good possibility that
Kim sent the money that he took from the K Corporation to his overseas account.
As long as we stick to K corporation,
We can prosecute him for oversees tax evasion,
tax evasion, bribery and embezzlement.
President Jo of the K Corporation didn't show up using illness as an excuse.
If we don't catch him, we'll end up...
But we don't have conclusive evidence.
Why are you obssessed with K Corporation?
Do you bear a deep grudge against them?
It's not like that.
You told me that the criminals would always be our enemies.
If we bend our rules depending on who they are...
This is an organization and we have our rules.
If you don't want to listen to me, you can resign.
I've told him.
When he heard that you are coming,
he started waiting for you with that bag.
I told him it's too hot to wear the jacket,
but he insisted on...
Dad!
You're here. Are you tired?
What? Are you tired after work?
No. Not at all.
Let's go home. I'm hungry.
Dad. Do you know what the date is today?
Your birthday is coming up.
Do you remember when your birthday is?
I'm hungry.
Right. You don't have to remember.
I'll remember your birthday.
You can just smile.
- Can you take care of this? - You have a visitor.
What are you doing here?
Do I surprise you with my sudden visit?
You came to me without an appointment.
If you're talking about the warrant...
I don't care about that.
Do you know what Kang Yoo Jung is doing now?
You already stopped her getting her parole.
- What do you want to do? - You can't say that.
You're the one who stopped her parole.
- How about having dinner together? - I already have plans.
Who's your date?
I don't want to share my private life with you.
I thought we were friends.
- Do you keep secrets from your friends? - Mr. Jo Min Hyuk!
Shina Foundation is hosting a charity event next week.
You can't meet those guests easily.
Make some connections.
I don't know how long those kinds of connections will last.
Take it easy.
I don't want to wrangle with you.
I just want to be friends with you.
I'll forget the thing
that you came to me with a warrant.
You've never been rejected, have you?
If you get bored, you give up.
If you fail, you find a new project.
You and I are completely different. We can never be friends.
Really? Let me think about it.
Are we really that different?
Yoo Jung!
This isn't the same as before.
After automatic fare collection system was introdued, many emplyees left.
Right.
How come you haven't contacted me?
Hae Ri left just after you quit.
She thought she could have a better life.
Can you contact Hae Ri?
Hello, I'm applying for the job you advertised on the newspaper.
Thank you. I'll see you tomorrow.
Do I have to go?
We'll open up a casino in our Hong Kong branch.
We need permission from the Hong Kong tourism organization.
Remember. Our goal is not to simply run a casino.
We're introducing the casino to them.
I know. But why do you need me there?
You're going by yourself this time.
What about you?
If you make it, your father will be very proud of you.
Why? This is no fun.
Fun?
You seem to live for fun.
Do something useful.
Take good care of him.
Yes.
Hey! Hey!
We haven't met each other for a while.
You stopped volunteering at the prison.
I've been busy.
Are you too busy to come to my art gallery?
Sorry?
Please come. You can make time if you want to.
Do you paint as well?
Hello. You're here.
I'll be expecting you.
How are you?
Fine.
You've been busy doing charity work.
It's not my project. I'm just helping my dad.
Are you coming to the party?
Of course.
How dare you come here?
I really want to kill you.
How dare you?
Sorry.
Ji Hee! My daughter.
My poor daughter!
Why do you come to torture me?
What are these?
Seo Ji Hee's mother sent these.
I'm sending back the money and the presents you gave me.
I don't figure out who sent these,
so it took me a long time to send them back.
I don't think my daughter would want this.
What can I do for her?
She won't take the house that I bought for her.
She doesn't want anything from me.
How do you think I can make Ji Hee happy?
What are you doing here?
Can't you just say hello?
Do I need an excuse to see you?
Is this for your exhibition?
It's not finished.
You can see it later.
What's bothering you?
How do you know that I'm troubled?
I've known you for such a long time.
I'm in a bad mood, but I don't know why.
You're a naive man.
Whether it's your anger toward her or your guilt,
forgive her and yourself.
Just let it go.
I wish it were that simple.
Stop!
Wait a moment.
Please stay still.
What are you doing?
It's dangerous for him to go out alone.
This has his information on it.
He can't take it off on his own.
- Just wati a minute. - No.
Please stay still.
You need this if you want to live with Yoo Jung.
It's ugly.
What do you mean? It's pretty.
Look, dad! Isn't it pretty?
This is our phone number.
Pretty.
What happened?
You're all wet.
I spilled something.
I'll go have a shower.
OK.
Lie down here.
It's late. Aren't you going home?
This is...
That's okay. It doesn't hurt any more.
It's not okay, you fool!
I'm sorry.
Don't be. It's not your fault.
It's all my fault.
Answer your phone.
I'll try harder.
I know you've been taking care of my father. I really appreciate it.
I'll visit your parents soon.
I haven't visited them after coming out of jail.
I'm sorry.
You'll be tired.
I know.
Sorry.
Why do you keep on saying sorry?
Stop saying sorry.
Sorry, no, no.
I got a job. I'll start working tomorrow.
What do you want to do?
Are you going to marry her?
I told you it's over after she's better.
No one can blame you.
You've done enough.
Please stop.
Even though she looks okay, she's still in great pain.
You only care about her. You never care about me.
It's all my fault. Yoo Jung and you.
Look! She's the one who should be blamed.
It's not her fault.
Then is it my fault?
I did everything to support you.
I know what you've done for me. Please stop.
How can you...
Honey.
What have you said to your mom?
I'm going to die.
I've done everything, yet he still blames me.
Calm down.
You called him San?
My heart breaks when I think about him,
but this might be the time to end this relationship.
Although you supprt each other now,
the kid will haunt both of you.
What if he were still alive?
Would it be different?
Can I marry her?
No.
Even if you two marry because of San,
who would bless your marriage?
You're going to have to lie about Yoo Jung
to your colleagues.
You'll end up quarreling with each other,
it brings you nothing but sorrow.
You and Yoo Jung weren't meant to be together.
Excuse me? More wine?
Your girlfriend is so pretty.
Enjoy your flight.
You should tell us the truth. Customers don't like it.
Hello.
Ms. Kang Yoo Jung? It's ‘Hangyeong Service.'
Yes?
Can you work as a waitress at K Art Center tomorrow night?
Sure. Thank you so much.
Prosecutor Ahn? You're coming tonight, right?
I didn't say that I'd be there.
I think you should.
What do you mean?
I'm your friend.
Why don't you trust me?
If you're invited, just go.
It's just a charity event.
Even the busiest prosecutors would attend that party.
Why are you so hesitated?
I'm jealous that Min Hyuk love you so much,
It's been 4 years since you passed away.
I think I've been patient enough.
Please let Min Hyuk go.
Please.
I'll tell my feeling to Min Hyuk today.
Excuse me!
Yoo Jung!
Unbelievable! Where have you been?
Are you ready?
When did you change the job?
Right after you left.
I was thinking about why I always ended up with bastards.
I needed to change my environment.
I didn't have to suffer in a big sea.
To catch one good fish.
There are lots of good fish here.
Have you caught one?
I have baited my hook, but none of them biting.
They have parties thanks to their rich parents.
What am I doing here?
Do you know who will be here today?
A rich princess of the Shina Foundation is hosting a charity party.
I guess all of the guests will be rich.
I'm poor. They should help me.
The time is limited. Let's hurry up.
- Hello, Prosecutor Ahn! - Hello.
Thank you for coming.
Hello.
Congratulations.
What are you doing?
Is this your new job?
No, this is my temp job.
What are you doing here?
I was invited. Lots of lawyers were invited.
It would embarrass you if I work here.
I haven't prepared dinner for my dad, he must be hungry now.
I have to go now.
Yoo Jung!
I'll help you to find a job where you can work daytime.
Go home and take care of your father.
Okay. I'll go now.
- Hello. - Congratulations!
Thank you. Enjoy your meal.
- Do Hoon. - Hello.
Why are you alone?
Sorry?
I saw you with a girl earlier. Who is she?
You don't want to talk about it?
Am I right?
It's good to see you here.
Why did you invite me here?
Please be patient.
You're here because you're curious, right?
Curiosity kill the cat.
Curiosity.
Hey!
I heard that you went to Hong Kong.
Yes. I went there for work. You wouldn't believe me though.
Did you have fun?
Jo Min Hyuk!
Can you stay until the end today?
No. I don't want to stay at this boring party.
Please try. I have something for you.
What is it? Give it to me now.
- No. - What is it?
If you're curious, then wait.
Only you can get it.
It must be something special.
It'll be fun. You like having fun, right?
Min Hyuk, I'm serious.
Stick around until the end.
See you later.
It hurts! Stop it! It hurts!
I have to do this.
Look how dirty you are!
If people see you like this, they'll blame me.
One more to go! The last one!
Bad girl!
Who's that?
It's done.
Prosecutor Ahn!
This is Hwang Changwoo, from JNJ Law firm.
You said he was your role model.
Prosecutor Ahn, I've heard a lot about you.
It's an honor to meet you.
I was impressed by the way you dealt with Congressman Kim's Case,
and the K Corporation.
You're ambitious. I like that.
Thank you.
We're going to form a global team,
and I was planning to meet you to discuss that.
I'll see you later.
I told you that you wouldn't regret it.
Where is Kang Yoo Jung? She's not here yet?
I'll check into it.
Go get her. I'm getting bored.
Okay.
Get out.
You're alive, yet you fooled us all along?
Sorry. Give me some more time. I'll definitely pay you back.
I can sue you for fraud.
Take these away.
Come on!
No! Stop!
What is this?
No!
What is it?
- What is it? - No! NO!
No! Stop.
No, no.
Who are you?
Who the hell are you?
What are you doing?
You can't do everything you want in someone else's house.
Someone else's house?
What? Have they already sold it?
What's going on?
I don't care.
- Kwang Soo, escort them out. - Yes.
Escort them out with respect.
Who are you?
Let me go.
Hey!
Why don't we talk outside?
What are you doing?
Treat them with respect, Kwang Soo.
What are you doing? Who are you?
Me? I'm the owner of this house.
That's the destiny.
I never sold this place. Get out of my house.
I never want to stay here.
I want you out by the end of this week.
If not, you'll be gone with this building.
No way! I've lived here my entire life. You have no right to do that.
Why do you keep torturing me and following me around? Who are you?
Why are you doing this to me?
What a bad person you are to treat me like this.
How can you do this to me?
Do you think what you did was okay?
How did it feel when you walked away from a dying person?
What I've done is nothing.
Compared to what you took away from me.
Hey! Was that you?
You can't just hit people and run away.
How dare you hurt what's mine?
Next on secret love.
You can stop following Kang Yoo Jung around.
Just leave her alone.
Dry your tears.
It's over.
- What? - This marriage.
I'm sorry.
Let me go! Aren't you ashamed of yourself?
Who is it?
You hurt Yoo Jung.
You remember that?
How can I forget.
You think I don't know that Yoo Jung is your scrapegoat?
Hey.
Is there anyone?
Don't die without my permission.